- What are you doing?
- Oh, Priya's calling in a few minutes...
(Leonard:)...on Skype
and we are gonna have a dinner date.
It's 8:00 in the morning in Mumbai.
(Sheldon:)How can she have dinner?
(Leonard:)Whatever.
Priya will be having breakfast.
(Sheldon:)All right.
So technically, it's not a dinner date.
(Sheldon:)I suppose you could call it
a, uh, dinfast date.
But if you did, you'd open yourseIf
to peer-based mocking...
...such as, "Hey, Leonard, how was
your dinfast with Priya last night?"
(Leonard:)That doesn't sound like mocking.
(Sheldon:)You didn't let me finish.
(Sheldon:)Dinfast.
(Sheldon:)Are those soy-based candles?
(Leonard:)I don't know. Why?
(Sheldon:)Paraffin candles
may contain carcinogens.
(Sheldon:)Unless lung cancer is the ambiance
you were going for at your dinfast.
(Sheldon:)Dinfast.
I don't wanna be rude,
but Priya's gonna be calling, so...
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. Priya.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you know I make a point...